Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Cuneiform Tablets, 1.25 linear feet in 1 small flat box
  - Two Cuneiform Tablets and Supporting Documentation (Including Translations), circa 2350 BC (Box 56)
- Series IV. Mummy Wrappings, .25 linear feet in 1 oversized folder
  - Two Mummy Wrappings (Box 45, Folder 2)